brinksprepaidmastercard.com 2019-06-09

# FACTS

                                                                                                                                                                   Rev. 10/2018
                                   WHAT DOES AXOS BANK™
 FACTS                             DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the
 Why?                              right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and
                                   protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.
                                   The information can include:
 What?                             • Social Security number and income
                                   • Account balances and overdraft history
                                   • Transaction history and employment information
                                   All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the
 How?                              section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the
                                   reasons Axos Bank™ chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                                                                                      Can you limit this
 Reasons we can share your personal Information                                                              Does Axos Bank share?
                                                                                                                                                            sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions,
 maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or                                             Yes                                  No
 report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and service to you                                                      Yes                                  No
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                                                         Yes                                  No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–
                                                                                                                            Yes                                  No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–
                                                                                                                            Yes                                 Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                                                        Yes                                 Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                                                         Yes                                 Yes
                                   • Call toll-free 1-800-273-1019; or
                                   • Mail the form below
                                   Please note:
 To limit our sharing
                                   If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice.
                                   When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                                   However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?                        Call toll-free 1-800-273-1019
 ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Mail-in Form
       Mark any/all you want to limit:
 q     Do not share information about my creditworthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business purposes.
       Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
       Do not share my personal information with nonaffiliates to market their products and servies to me.
 Name
 Account Number                                                                                             Mail To:
                                                                                                            Netspend Corp
 Address                                                                                                    Privacy Choice
                                                                                                            P.O. Box 2136
 City, State, ZIP                                                                                           Austin, TX 78768-2136
 Phone Number
0200-4

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing notice?                   Axos Bank, also known as UFB Direct.
What we do
                                           To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
                                           measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and
How does Axos Bank protect my              secured files and buildings.
personal information?
                                           We restrict access to your personal information to our employees who need to know that
                                           information to provide your products and services.
                                           We collect your personal information, for example, when you
                                           • Open an account or deposit money
How does Axos Bank collect my              • Provide account information or provide employment information
personal information?                      • Use your credit or debit card
                                           We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or
                                           other companies.
                                           Federal law gives you to right to limit only
                                           • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
                                           • affiliates from using your information to market to you
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
                                           • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                           State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See
                                           below from more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing
for an account I hold jointly with         Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
someone else?
Definitions
                                           Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
Affiliates                                 nonfinancial companies.
                                           • Our affiliates include companies with a common corporate identity or name.
                                           Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                           nonfinancial companies.
Nonaffiliates
                                           • Nonaffiliates we share with can include tax preparation companies, insurance companies,
                                              direct marketing companies, nonprofit organizations, and other banks.
                                           A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                           financial products or services to you.
Joint Marketing
                                           • Our joint marketing partners include finance companies, mortgage companies, insurance
                                              companies and investment companies.
Other important information
You may have privacy rights under various state laws including Vermont, California and Nevada. Axos Bank will comply with these
laws to the extent they apply. We may telephone existing customers with offers for additional financial products. You have the right
to opt-out of this contact by calling 1-800-273-1019 to add your name to our do-not- call/contact list. Nevada residents may also
contact the Nevada Attorney General for opt out information by phone (775-684-1100); email (bcpinfo@ag.state.nv.us); or mail
(100 N. Carson St., Carson City, NV 89701). We may share your personal information with offshore service providers, for the limited
purpose of providing a customer service call center for certain of the bank’s products and services.
                                                                                                                         F03-X381-8  3830548
